clickpromise.com 2009-12-23

# ClickPromise.com - Email Marketing * List Management

**Our Privacy Policy**

We understand your potential privacy concerns especially in today's ever changing internet world. Since we do share your information with other third parties as outlined in this policy, we urge you to take the time to fully review this policy and to make sure it meets your personal expectations on privacy. If it fails to meet your expectations of privacy, we strongly urge you to not register on any of our sites.

When you register with us or on any of our sites, we do sell your registration information such as but not limited to your name, telephone number, email address, and street address to other third parties. If you do not want us to sell such information to other third parties, then please do not register with us or on any of our sites. 

**What Do We Do With Registration Information?**

We may ask you to give us contact and demographic information when you register. We use this information to send our Site's users like you information about the Site. We also use this information to contact you and to send you promotional offers both on line and offline. We also use your registration information when we sell, rent, or otherwise share such information with other third parties to promote their offers. You may opt-out of receiving any future mailings by following our opt-out procedures. See the choice/opt-out section below. 

**What Do We Do With Cookies and IP Address Information?**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit our site. You may set your browser to refuse cookies. If you make that choice, please understand that you may not be eligible for any specials and / or promotions we may offer our Site’s users. 

**How Do We Work with Other Companies and How Does That Affect Our Privacy Policy?**

As stated earlier, we may sell your registration information to other third parties such as our affiliates, sponsors, partners, and the like. In so doing, we provide links to other sites. Unfortunately, unless we control such sites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such other sites. Consequently, to the extent you are not satisfied with other third parties having access to your registration information, please do not register with us or on any of our sites. 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on this Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Do We Share Personal Information?**

We adhere to the policy of permission sharing only. If you give us permission, we share your personal information with other companies we select. We select companies we believe offer products and services that add to our portfolio and that would be beneficial to you. By registering with us or on any of our sites, you specifically grant us permission to sell, rent, or otherwise share your registration information with other third parties. 

**How Do Our Users Change Information Previously Entered and/or Opt-Out of Receiving Information?**

We firmly believe you should easily be able to make changes to your personal information and / or opt out at anytime. We allow you to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our affiliates / partners / sponsors when we request information about you. This Site allows you to authorize our use of your personal information as follows:

  1. I authorize ClickPromise.com ("ClickPromise") to mail me regarding promotional information.
  2. I authorize ClickPromise to email me promotional information.
  3. I authorize ClickPromise to sell, rent, or otherwise share my registration information with any third party entities selected by ClickPromise.

**Choice/Opt-Out Procedures**

We allow you to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our affiliates / partners / sponsors when we request information about you. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by e-mail or by posting a prominent announcement on our landing page. 

**PARENTS: Please Note Our Privacy Policy Regarding Children**

Given the ever increasing exchange of information and materials in today’s internet world, we are extremely sensitive to privacy issues especially when it comes to children. Therefore, we are especially careful in any communications involving children and their families. We do not knowingly collect any information whatsoever from children 13 and under. We do not verify the age of any registrant and simply rely on the veracity of any registrant when such registrant provides us with information. Consequently, if you are uncomfortable with this lack of verification procedures, we urge you to not register with us or on any of our sites. We treat any child over the age of 13, as disclosed to us in the registration process, the same way as we treat all other registrants. 

We urge parents to regularly monitor and supervise their children's on-line activities. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or use of our trademarks and copyrighted material, please contact us at the address below. For any other concerns about this Site, please go to[ http://www.clickpromise.com/contact.asp](http://www.clickpromise.com/contact.asp).
